Guide to the Vice President for Finance and Administration Records, 1819-2017
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vice President for Finance and Administration Records
1819-2017
Vassar College. Vice President for Finance and Administration
46 cubic feet (46 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Materials relating to the financial and business operations of the college. Includes restricted material.
Administrative History
The office of the Vice President for Administration was created in 1966 by the Board of Trustees, which unified Vassar's Business Administration department. James Ritterskamp became the first Vice President for Administration in 1966 and served in this position until 1981. He was succeeded by Anthony Stellato in 1983, who held the position until his retirement in 2000. The office was created to handle non-academic matters of the College including purchases and debts, the maintenance of buildings and grounds, and non-academic personnel. These tasks had previously been the duties of the comptroller. In 1981, the Vice President for Administration was combined with the Vice President for Student Services to become the Vice President for Administrative and Student Services, increasing the duties of the office to include campus activities food service, communications, financial aid, health services, security, residence, and publication. This position was also briefly known as Treasurer and Chief Financial Officer. In 1985, it became the Vice President for Finance and included the duties of the college treasurer, and 2001, the position officially became the Vice President for Finance and Administration. Offices which report to the Vice President for Finance and Administration include: the Controller, Facilities Operations, the Budget and Planning Office, Investments, Accounting Services, and Procurement.
Source: Strickland, Karilyn and Marian Thomas. An Administrative History of Vassar College, 1861-2003. Edited by Ronald D. Patkus and Elizabeth A. Daniels. Poughkeepsie, NY: Vassar College, 2004.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains the records of two Vice Presidents of Finance and Administration, Anthony Stellato and James Ritterskamp, as well as earlier and later materials. The collection consists of correspondence, records, and memoranda relating to the financial and business operations of the college, including property and committee records.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into three series by accession group: Series I. James Ritterskamp Files; Series II. Anthony Stellato Files; and Series III. 2025 Addition.
Access
Some materials in this collection are closed to research. Files will need to be reviewed before being released for research. This collection is stored off-site and requires advance notification for use. If ordered Monday-Thursday we can generally guarantee delivery for the next day Please contact the Library Staff for more information.
Related Materials
Vassar College Controller's Office Records
Vassar College Facilities Operations Records
Vassar College Office of the Treasurer Records
Subject Headings
Names:
Vassar, Matthew, 1792-1868; Ritterskamp, James J.; Stellato, Anthony
Organizations:
Vassar College--Finances; Vassar College--Buildings; Vassar College--Administration
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Document Types:
Clippings; Contracts; Correspondence; Deeds; Financial records; Minutes (administrative records); Property Records; Reports; Tax Records
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Administrative Offices and Functions
Encoding Information
Encoded by Elizabeth Clarke, August 2007. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, 2022-2025.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Office of the Vice President for Finance and Administration in three accessions: August 2007 (A2007-031 and A2007-046) and May 2025 (A2025-018).
Other Finding Aids
Some names have been redacted from the container listing. A full listing (ms word doc) is available to Archives and Special Collections staff.
Series List
- Series I. James Ritterskamp Files, 1948-1981; (Boxes 20-35)
  This series primarily contains records from James Ritterskamp's tenure as Vice President for Finance and Administration, a position he held from 1966 until 1981.
  Arranged alphabetically by file title.
- Series II. Anthony Stellato Files, 1983-2000; (Boxes 1-19, 35)
  This series primarily contains records from Anthony Stellato's tenure as Vice President for Finance and Administration, a position he held from 1981 to 2000.
  Arranged in no particular order.
- Series III. 2025 Addition, 1819-2017; (Boxes 36-46)
  This series consists of records created or maintained by the office of the Vice President for Finance and Administration from its creation in 1966 until approximately 2017. In particular, this series contains property records kept by the office, including deeds, titles, abstracts of title, easements, leases, and other contracts, as well as construction documents, reports, assessments, and correspondence. Also included are committee minutes and other records, bond records, tax forms, Middle States Association records, and other documents produced by the office.
  Organized into six subseries by record type: Property Records, Committee Records, Bond Records, Middle States Association Self-Study Records, Miscellaneous Records, and Tax Forms 990 and 990T.
Container List
- Series I. James Ritterskamp Files, 1966-1981
  - College Administrative Procedure Manual, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - College Administrative Retreat, 1977-1981 (Box 20)
  - College Administrative Retreat, 1979-1980 (Box 20)
  - College Administrative Staff, 1964-1980 (Box 20)
  - College Center Art Gallery, 1978-1977 (Box 20)
  - College: AAUP Releases, 1969-1976 (Box 20)
  - College: AAUP Reports, 1955-1979 (Box 20)
  - College: AAUP Reports Faculty Salaries, 1966-1979 (Box 20)
  - College: Alumnae House, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - College: Antolini, Julia, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - College: Archives and Records, 1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Baldwin North, Jane, 1973 (Box 20)
  - College: Bicentennial Celebration, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - College: Blanding Gibson, Sarah, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - College: Buckley Amendment on School Records, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - College: By-Laws and Governance, 1977-1979 (Box 20)
  - College: Cambridge Associates, Inc, 1979-1981 (Box 20)
  - College: Campus Activities and Music License Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
  - College: Career Development, 1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Commencements and Convocations, 1969-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Committee to Review Special Fees, 1966 (Box 20)
  - College: Communications Office, 1976-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Community Breakfast, 1975-1977 (Box 20)
  - College: Community Relations, 1968-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Comptrollers Office, 1969-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Comptrollers Search, 1979-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Conservation, 1971-1974 (Box 20)
  - College: Consulting Architect (Hutchins), 1966-1969 (Box 20)
  - College: Consulting Architect (Hutchins), 1972-1979 (Box 20)
  - College: Contracts for Outside Performances, 1972-1975 (Box 20)
  - College: Correspondence: President’s Office, 1972-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Correspondence: Vice President for Student Affairs, 1969-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Curriculum, 1978-1981 (Box 20)
  - College: Dormitories, 1971-1977 (Box 20)
  - College: Dormitory Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 20)
  - College: Drinking Water, 1977 (Box 20)
  - College: Ecological Field Station, 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - College: Emergency Procedures First Aid, 1976-1977 (Box 20)
  - College: Emergency Use of Facilities, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
  - College: EMT, 1977 (Box 20)
  - College: Enrollment Statistics, 1967-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Fact Sheet on Vassar College, 1976 (Box 20)
  - College: Faculty Benefits, 1967 (Box 20)
  - College: Faculty Steering Committee, 1968 (Box 20)
  - College: Famine Relief, 1974-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Fellowships and Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Box 20)
  - College: Stores, 1979-1980 (Box 20)
  - College: Financial Statements, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - College: Financial Aid, 1977-1980 (Box 21)
  - College: Foundations: Appeals, Proposals, 1966 (Box 21)
  - College: Fund, 1971 (Box 21)
  - College: Gilbert, Mary J., 1980 (Box 21)
  - College: Gooding, Velma, 1977 (Box 21)
  - College: Growth of the College, 1971-1977 (Box 21)
  - College: Historic Preservation, 1981 (Box 21)
  - College: Honors and Awards, 1972-1979 (Box 21)
  - College: Housefellows, 1971-1981 (Box 21)
  - College: IBM, 1975-1979 (Box 21)
  - College: Inauguration of Virginia B. Smith, 1978 (Box 21)
  - College: Insurance: Faculty – TIAA CREF, 1966-1968 (Box 21)
  - College: Insurance: Buildings, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - College: Insurance: Buildings, 1966-1968 (Box 21)
  - College: Institute of World Affairs, 1976-1977 (Box 21)
  - College: Latest Uproar, Dec. 1073 Version, 1973 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Aspects and Decisions, 1968 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Decisions, 1969 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Lars Erickson, Robin McMahon, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Lars Erickson, Robin McMahon, 1974 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Joan Finley, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Douglas Fleming, 1979 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Leona Gardner, 1980 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Nancy Graber, 1973-1976 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Ellen Kanner, 1979 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Helen Pappas, 1976 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Patricia Singer, undated (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Valerie Merkerson, 1981 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Case – Jeffrey Wallach, undated (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Opinions, 1966-1974 (Box 21)
  - College: Legal Opinions, 1975-1981 (Box 21)
  - College: Life Income Plan, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - College: Loyalty Oath, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - College: Millbank, Tweed, Hadley and McCloy, 1980-1981 (Box 21)
  - College: Management Consultants, 1968-1979 (Box 21)
  - College: Memberships and Subscriptions, 1967-1977 (Box 21)
  - College: Housing Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - College: Subcommittee on Faculty Housing, 1960-1966 (Box 21)
  - College: Faculty Housing Eligibility, 1973-1981 (Box 22)
  - College: Housing, 1966-1968 (Box 22)
  - College: Faculty Housing Rentals, 1974-1981 (Box 22)
  - College: Interior Decorating Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - College: Campus Lighting, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
  - College: November 12 Student/Faculty Coalition, 1976 (Box 22)
  - College: Office of Institutional Research, 1972 (Box 22)
  - College: Carolyn Paschal, 1980 (Box 22)
  - College: Summary Plan Descriptions, 1978-1979 (Box 22)
  - College: Management Letters, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - College: Meal Contracts, 1979 (Box 22)
  - College: Middle States Evaluation, 1977-1979 (Box 22)
  - College: Middle States Accreditation, 1969-1979 (Box 22)
  - College: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967-1980 (Box 22)
  - College: Noyes, 1974 (Box 22)
  - College: Organization Charts, 1976-1978 (Box 22)
  - College: Outside Use of Facilities, 1966-1967 (Box 22)
  - College: Payroll Legislation Information, 1966 (Box 22)
  - College: Personnel Problems, 1977 (Box 22)
  - College: Poughkeepsie Day School Planning Committee, 1967-1973 (Box 22)
  - College: 1977 President Report (Box 22)
  - College: 1971-1972 President Report (Box 22)
  - College: President’s Report, 1970-1976 (Box 22)
  - College: Purchase Contracts/Vassar College, 1975 (Box 22)
  - College: Quitclaim Deeds, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - College: Radio Station, 1969-1979 (Box 22)
  - College: Return Policy, 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - College: Records Retention, 1977 (Box 22)
  - College: Regulations Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 22)
  - College: Security, 1973-1975 (Box 22)
  - College: Self Study, 1977-1980 (Box 22)
  - College: 7 College Conference, 1968-1976 (Box 22)
  - College: Simpson, Alan, 1973-1980 (Box 22)
  - College: Smith, Virginia, 1980 (Box 22)
  - College: Space Allocation, 1966 (Box 22)
  - College: Speakers: Arrangements Facilities, 1968 (Box 23)
  - College: Staff Compensation, 1974-1977 (Box 23)
  - College: Stellato, Anthony, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
  - College: Student Fellow Program, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - College: Studies Abroad India, 1969 (Box 23)
  - College: Studies Abroad Madrid, 1970 (Box 23)
  - College: Studies Abroad Rome, 1968-1969 (Box 23)
  - College: Summer Programs, 1970-1980 (Box 23)
  - College: Summer Programs Use of Tennis Courts and Swimming Pool, 1976-1980 (Box 23)
  - College: Travel Program, 1972 (Box 23)
  - College: Twelve College Exchange, 1970-1975 (Box 23)
  - College: Unemployment Comp, 1977 (Box 23)
  - College: Union Classroom Space, 1969-1973 (Box 23)
  - College: Vassar College Staff Association, 1973-1979 (Box 23)
  - College: Vassar Dump, undated (Box 23)
  - College: Vassar Farm Tax Grievance, 1976-1978 (Box 23)
  - College: Vassar Farm Tax Grievance, 1976 (Box 23)
  - College: Vassar Priorities, 1974-1980 (Box 23)
  - College: Vassar-Wesleyan Program, 1976-1979 (Box 23)
  - College: Withdrawals, 1972-1976 (Box 23)
  - College: State of NY Dept of Transportation, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Faculty: Building Sites – Patricia Johnson, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Faculty: Housing – Mortgage Funds, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Alumnae House, 1978-1980 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations, 1948-1977 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Bardavon and Juliet Theaters, 1972-1976 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Boiler Conversion, 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Boiler Conversion, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Cablevision, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Casperkill Creek, 1971-1975 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: 37 Collegeview Avenue, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Collegeview Avenue, 1971-1999 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Correspondence, 1966-1975 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Dean’s House, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Energy, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Dept of Transportation, 1981 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Dept of Transportation East West Arterial, 1976-1978 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Dormitory Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Drop-in Center, 1972-1978 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Duggan House, 1972-1980 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Electricity, 1968-1980 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Expenditures, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Fire Dept, 1967-1970 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Fire Safety, 1969-1981 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Fire Watchers, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Fuel, 1973-1981 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Fulton Avenue Variance, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Greenhouse, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: 360 Hooker Avenue, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Hooker Avenue, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Grounds, 1975-1981 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Heat Control – Dormitories, 1977-1980 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Horticulturist, 1975-1977 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: Horticulturist – David Stoller, 1977-1980 (Box 23)
  - Plant Operations: IBM – Summer Housing, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: IBM System, 1974-1977 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Ice Skating Rink, 1968-1973 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Interior Decorating Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Lathrop Intercultural Center, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Laundry Room Main Building, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Lighting on Campus, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Retreat Matthew’s Mug, 1970-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Miller Property, 1968-1970 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Movie Projection Facilities, 1972-1977 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Murphy House, 1970-1979 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Murphy Property, 1967-1977 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Olmstead Hall, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Personnel, 1968-1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Power Dept, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Prentiss Field, 1973-1978 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: President’s House, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Raymond Avenue Traffic Lights, 1971-1989 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Recycling Program, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Regulations, 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Repairs and Maintenance, 1967-1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Rights of Way, 1968-1970 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Riding Stable, 1969-1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Rugby Field, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Safety Committee, 1961-1979 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Security, 1975-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Campus Security, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Security – Special Investigation, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Cushing Incident, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Security Study, 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Security Consultant, 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Security Incident – Hodges, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Security Vandalism and Robberies, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Service Building, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Shakespeare Gardens, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Sound System, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Space Study, 1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Sprinklers, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Outside use of Facilities, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: State Acquisition of College Property, 1968-1973 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Tennis Courts, 1968-1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Thelberg Road Area, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Traffic Parking, 1970-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Trash Removal, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Townhouses and Terrace Apartments, 1971-1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Vassar College Properties, 1966-1980 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Vassar Farm, 1975-1981 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Vehicles, 1972-1977 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Walk: Main Building to Library, 1968 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Weather, 1975-1978 (Box 24)
  - Plant Operations: Woodworkings and Ceramics Shops, 1972-1980 (Box 24)
  - College: Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College Reunion Weekend, 1980 (Box 24)
  - College: Alumnae and Alumni of Vassar College, 1978 (Box 24)
  - College: Vassar AAVC Gift Recording Study, 1973 (Box 24)
  - College: Development Office – AAVC Fundraising, 1980 (Box 24)
  - College: Development Office – National Council, 1980 (Box 24)
  - College: Development Office, 1979-1981 (Box 25)
  - College: Development Office, 1976-1979 (Box 25)
  - College: Development Office: Kresge Grant, 1975-1977 (Box 25)
  - College: Development Office: Alaska Farm, 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - College: Development Office: Robert Nelson Study, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Allocations, 1979 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Annuity Fund, 1971-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Audit – Student Loans, 1975-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Banks and Banking Activities, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Bequest Pending Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 25)
  - Finances: College Center, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Audit, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Consolidated Investment Fund, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Cost Comparisons With Other Private Institutions, 1970-1979 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Research Overhead Recovery, 1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Inflation Contingent Account, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Capital Campaign 1972-1973, 1972-1975 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Capital Campaign Industry Drive, 1970-1972 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Capital Campaign 1973-1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Capital Campaign MTS, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Development: Capital Campaign (Offices and Equipment), 1968-1973 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Campaign Position Paper, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Education and Tuition Funds and Plans, 1968-1971 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Endowment/Student Report, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Equipment Needs, 1969-1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Construction Funding, 1969-1975 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Fellowships and Scholarships, 1968-1971 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Financial Aid, 1979-1981 (Box 25)
  - Finances: The Financial Picture of Vassar College, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Financial Statements and General Material, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Fringe Benefits, 1968-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Foundations: Appeal, Proposals, 1965-1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Funds for Higher Education, 1971 (Box 25)
  - Finances: General Service Foundation Gift, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Gift Analysis, 1968-1978 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Hollins College Report, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Institutional Securities Corporation, 1971-1977 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Internal Revenue Service, 1968-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: IRS Ruling re Contribution of Securities, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Legal Fees, 1968-1980 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Summary Statements, 1971-1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Telephone, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Tuition – Other Colleges, 1968-1981 (Box 25)
  - Finances: Tuition Rates, 1980-1981 (Box 25)
  - Finance: Tuition Remission Plan, 1963-1980 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Uncollectible Accounts, 1971-1978 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Tuition – Protest Letters, 1977 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Payroll, 1967-1980 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Refund Policy, 1975-1980 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Stock Loans, 1973-1975 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Student Accounts, 1971-1978 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Taxes, 1973-1977 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Tax Exemptions, 1967-1980 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Terrace Apartments, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Loan of Securities, 1968-1980 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Investment of Idle Cash, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Investors Report 1970 (Box 26)
  - Finance: Total Return Concept, 1979 (Box 26)
  - Black Studies Program, 1972-1975 (Box 26)
  - Future Programs – Black Studies Program, 1969-1972 (Box 26)
  - College: Black Studies Program, 1969 (Box 26)
  - College: Black Studies Program, 1973-1975 (Box 26)
  - Black Studies: Evaluation and Future Development, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - College Black Studies Program – Kendrick House, 1971-1975 (Box 26)
  - Black Studies Program – Ramey Case, 1972-1976 (Box 26)
  - Black Studies Summer Program, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Black Studies Program - Sickle Cell Anemia Program, 1971-1972 (Box 26)
  - College Black Studies Program 1969 Reports (Box 26)
  - College Committees: Joint Committee of Minority Students at Vassar, 1970 (Box 26)
  - College: Black Studies Program: Urban Center, 1969-1979 (Box 26)
  - College Committee Advisory, 1970 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Master Planning Committee, 1979 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Master Planning Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Master Planning Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Master Planning Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Master Planning Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Committee for Master Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Committee for Master Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Committee for Master Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 27)
  - Future Programs Campus Committee for Master Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - Future Programs Campus Committee for Master Planning, 1969-1970 (Box 27)
  - Subcommittee on an Arts Center, undated (Box 27)
  - Subcommittee to Develop Space Requirements for College Center, 1970-1972 (Box 27)
  - Dormitory Occupancy Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Forever Green Subcommittee, 1972-1980 (Box 27)
  - Campus Planning Faculty Club, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Subcommittee on Recreational Space, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Committees: CMPC Subcommittee on Recreational Space, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Master Planning, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Dormitory Occupancy Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Campus Budget Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Faculty Policy and Conference Committee, 1970-1978 (Box 27)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1978-1979 (Box 27)
  - Committees: Faculty Appointments and Salary Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 27)